The Christmas Train is a family, tv movie, drama film directed by Ron Oliver.
Forced to take the intercontinental trip to Los Angeles by train, and determined to chronicle his adventure,
disillusioned journalist Tom Langdon finds himself westbound with a variety of characters.
While all passengers on the Christmas train appear to be headed for the same destination, Tom has no idea that
the rugged locomotives taking him across America will instead detour straight into his heart.
Tom Langdon, played by Dermot Mulroney.
Eleanor Carter, played by Kimberly Williams-Paisley.
Max Powers, played by Danny Glover.
Agnes, played by Joan Cusack.
Lelia, played by Holly Dignard.
Julie, played by Kirsten Zien.
The Christmas Train is a 2017 American Christmas romantic drama television film directed by Ron Oliver and written
by Neal Dobrofsky and Tippi Dobrofsky, based on the 2003 novel of the same name by David Baldacci.
The film stars Dermot Mulroney, Kimberly
Williams-Paisley, Danny Glover, and Joan Cusack.
The film premiered on Hallmark Hall of Fame, the Hallmark Channel,
and Hallmark Movies & Mysteries on November 25, 2017.
The tone is emotional.